The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
An Ascendant cultivation ?
I'm in a good mood today.
If you put that thing down,
I will pretend nothing happened
and let you leave.
You're courting death !
Your devil spells
are weaker than
the scattered devil's.
Something's wrong !
Dong Lin Screen !
He does have some skill for withstanding a full-power strike
from the Celestial Guard.
For you to force me to materialize my Dao...
You indeed deserve to die !
Devil Transformation Lotus Dao...
Turn !
This demonic lotus attacks the mind directly.
If you want a battle of Dao,
I will play along with you !
This man is just a first step cultivator
but he already materialized his Dao !?
Turn again !
Condense the river's soul !
Your Dao
is too weak !
What is this whip !?
How can it shake my Dao Heart !?
How is this possible ?
My cultivation is above his.
I can't possibly lose !
Stop !
What are you going to do ?
Xu Liguo !
Little Xu is here !
What kind of monster was that !?
Kid,
your Grandpa Xu
is a Sword Spirit that inherited an ancient sword intent.
Dying by my hand
should be an honor.
Impossible !
He should've been just an Ascendant cultivator !
Master, Master,
how did Little Xu perform ?
This duel caused quite a commotion.
I should move.
When hunting for treasures in this Celestial Realm,
I can avoid powerful enemies.
But the human heart
is unpredictable.
Mountains\NThunder Celestial Realm fragment
Hurry up !
That's a Celestial restriction !
Fellow cultivators,
let's join forces to break this restriction.
Yuan Ningwang\NSoul Transformation
I'm sure there's a treasure inside !
It was a trap !
There are too many people
with such low cultivations.
Ge Hong\NPeak Late stage Ascendant
They couldn't even fill the gaps between the Heavenly Ghost's teeth.
Li Yuan,
weren't you supposed to be unmatched in the art of restrictions ?
Are you incompetent
or did you simply not put in the effort ?
Li Yuan\NPeak Late stage Ascendant
My Lady, forgive me.
I was ordered by Family Head Ge to assist you.
I won't dare to be negligent !
The next meal
has arrived.
This restriction contains a trace of celestial spiritual energy.
But this celestial spiritual energy isn't perfectly merged.
The one who made this restriction
is very skilled.
He wouldn't have made such a mistake.
What's wrong with this person ?
Did he just
see through it ?
Why did he leave ?
Li Yuan,
why wasn't that person fooled ?
Don't forget,
your Life Soul is in my hands.
With just a single thought,
I can make your life a hell
where you can neither live nor die.
My Lady...
Perhaps that person was perceptive enough
to notice something was off.
We will find someone else.
Find someone else ?
Who gave you the right to decide my affairs !?
He was able to deduce my hiding spot from the restriction ?
This person's understanding and control over restrictions
is not inferior to mine.
So he didn't fall into the trap
but still came to me.
Stop.
Go.
Li Yuan,
if I die, you won't survive !
So it really was the 18 Plum Blossoms Restriction.
He actually recognized the 18 Plum Blossoms Restriction ?
Heavenly Ghost,
devour him !
This ghost isn't too bad.
It's a good material for refining Celestial Guards.
This celestial spirit
was nurtured by my family for a thousand years !
How dare you...
How dare you !
Noisy...
Fellow cultivator,
please show us mercy !
My Lady is young and impetuous
and was rude to you.
I must
apologize on her behalf.
I know a secret fragment of the Thunder Celestial Realm
where there is a complete origin tool.
We are willing to guide you there.
Whatever we obtain there
will be split evenly
between you and the Ge Family.
Fellow cultivator,
what do you think ?
That's my Ge Family's secret !
Li Yuan,
you !
This guy can break my restrictions
and capture the Heavenly Ghost.
He's not an ordinary Ascendant cultivator.
If you were to die here,
I would've failed the task the Family Head gave me.
My Lady,
What's more important ?
Earlier, I saw that his Life Soul
is in that woman's hands.
He was very submissive and compliant
so I thought nothing of him.
But judging by his words just now,
he doesn't seem like the type of person that can be controlled by others.
Moreover, the restriction he used was the 18 Plum Blossoms Restriction.
A person of this caliber
is not ordinary.
The origin tool might not exist
but if I can have the opportunity to master this restriction,
it would make that trip worth it.
I accept
this deal.
But I want to extract a Life Soul
as a guarantee.
You wouldn't dare !
Fellow cultivator,
why not take mine instead ?
Lead the way.
My Lady...
You're useless.
3 days later
Edge of the\NCelestial Realm fragment
The signs of destruction here
are similar to those of the Rain Celestial Realm's palmprint.
What kind of calamity
did the ancient Celestial Realms suffer
for them to collapse like this ?
This thunder area
is the only way to the secret fragment.
Apparently,
this thunder contains a trace
of residual energy from the collapse of the Celestial Realm.
Even Corporeal Yang cultivators
can be annihilated by it if they aren't careful.
But Brother Xu doesn't need to worry,
the Ge Family's heirloom artifact can ward off thunder.
It will help us to cross this place.
Let's go.
Brother Xu...
My Lady...
I want him to know
that without my Thunder-Warding Sword,
he can't take a single step inside.
Then I can use that as a reason
to take my Life Soul back.
He can actually cross the thunder with his physical body ?
Maybe...
he'll really help me to achieve my goal.
That's...
This is not a living being,
it's formed by an extremely profound restriction.
By using the fragments of the Thunder Celestial Realm as its foundation,
and a soul-like object as its restriction eye,
this great formation can refine everything under the heavens.
The one who made this formation
likely had a cultivation beyond Nirvana Cleanser.
Although this thing is terrifying,
my thunder physical body
shares the same origin
so it should be able to resist.
Between Ge Hong and Li Yuan,
Ge Hong leads the way on the surface,
but Li Yuan seems to be the one truly in control.
What is he after ?
I can use this thing
to test Li Yuan's abilities.
It's been a long time...
He seems even more familiar
with the Ge Family's artifact than Ge Hong is.
What happened
just now ?
Thank you, Brother Xu.
Li Yuan...
What are you hiding ?
My Lady,
hold on a little longer.
There are more restrictions ahead
but the secret fragment is close.
Half a month later
Celestial Graveyard\NThunder Celestial Realm
Master,
there is a strong ancient sword intent.
I feel
something is not right.
Where are we ?
The legend says that during the collapse of the Thunder Celestial Realm,
a general of the Celestial Realm was buried here.
He and his sword died here in battle,
the sword fell and became a mountain.
It's this mountain.
Who knows if there's an origin tool here.
Something's wrong...
Finally...
This figure...
Grandfather,
who is this person ?
A Celestial slave.
His family and my Ge Family
have a blood feud.
Fortunately,
they have been wiped out.
Impossible...
An ancient slave imprint ?
You...
Who the hell are you !?
Li Yuan
from the Li Family of Planet Annihilation,
the last direct descendant of the 37th generation.
30 000 years ago,
my Ancestor was branded with a slave imprint here by a remnant Celestial soul.
The Li Family's bloodline
withered after that.
This sword
was forged from the flesh, blood, and souls of half of my Li Family.
It was created specifically to break the slave imprint.
10 000 years ago, my ancestor Li Jinglan came here with this sword
to sever the slave imprint.
But he was ambushed and robbed by your Ge Family's Ancestor, Ge Yunfeng,
and failed.
I...
I have your Life Soul !
With a single thought...
You can try.
Life Soul,
come out !
How can this be ?
Back then,
my Ancestor was branded with a slave imprint here
but he also learned the truth of this place.
Every blade of grass, every tree,
every mountain, every rock,
is condensed from the Annihilation Restriction.
Your Ge Family thought that by holding my Life Soul,
you would be safe.
But you didn't know that
on this Annihilation Restriction Mountain,
taking it back
is as easy as flipping my hand.
Li Yuan...
My Ge Family is a great Family of Allheaven !
You, a servant from a fallen family,
would dare to kill me !?
Ge Family...
Did you think
that every time I bowed my head to serve you tea,
every time I kneeled,
every punishment I endured...
What did you think those years were for ?
Every day,
I used this restriction to carve a stroke into your Sea of Consciousness
to make you trust me and rely on me,
to make your grandfather order me to protect you here.
The Illusion Heart Restriction ?
You deceived my Ge Family from the very start...
You treacherous scoundrel !
If I didn't do it,
how long would I have needed to wait for you
to return this sword to me ?
Today,
I shall fulfill my Ancestor's final wish.
I will use this sword to sever my family's slave imprint.
And use your blood
as a sacrifice to my Li Family
for the ancestral souls that have waited for tens of thousands of years !
My Lady...
Do you understand now ?
18 Plum Blossoms Restriction
The Life Soul is the same thing as the Soul Blood but for higher level cultivators.\N\NA lot of things are getting skipped and changed here.\N1- Wang Lin absorbed Xu Fenghan's materialization of his Dao inside his Underworld River. Xu Fenghan didn't store any items in bags of holding but stored them inside a folded space he created in the materialization of his Lotus Dao, there were some items inside. By the way, Xu Fenghan comes from planet Dong Lin (the planet Wang Lin wants to reach to revive Li Muwan).\N2- Fragments of the Thunder Celestial Realm are linked by chains. Wang Lin doesn't walk in the void but walks on the chains and they follow the chains to find the secret fragment.\N3- It doesn't make any sense for Wang Lin to be able to stop the restriction they find in the void. In the novel, that restriction was set by Master Flamespark which they also meet in the void. Master Flamespark had decided that Wang Lin and him are fated and he asks Wang Lin to give him his silver-horned Thunder Beast. In exchange, he helps Wang Lin's cultivation. After that he helps the trio to cross the void to reach the secret fragment.\NHe looked at Wang Lin and said, “Your cultivation is a mess. A thunder origin soul and a thunder body, what is this? Let this old man give you a helping hand!”\NThe old man’s right hand reached out and a large amount of dust gathered in his hand to form a ball of light. He then spat out a mouthful of energy into the ball of light and threw it without even looking. The ball of light shot directly toward Wang Lin.\NThe old man’s body flickered and then he disappeared with the Thunder Beast. However, almost right after he reappeared, he looked at where Wang Lin disappeared to and muttered, “Just then how much energy did I put into it? Uh… It seems I put a little too much… That little guy should be alright… Regardless, if he doesn’t die, then he really is fated with this old man.”\N4- After that and during the following 20 chapters, Wang Lin is in constant agony trying to suppress the ball of light Master Flamespark gave him to prevent himself from dying on the spot.\NHis body trembled. This feeling was like when a mortal swallowed a piece of burning coal. Unimaginable heat was coming from inside his body as if it was trying to burn his entire body to dust.\N5- In the novel, Li Yuan gives more details about his Ancestors. But the main change is that the donghua added the whole mind-control of the Ge Family subplot which is awesome and very fitting of Li Yuan.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.